Wirawat Tumtongdee

Software Developer

- wirawat.tum@outlook.com 🤳 0960081874
- 🐴 188/938 condo notting hill sukhuvit praksa Tai Ban Mai Subdistrict, 10280 Samut Prakan
- in linkedin.com/in/cmd-mdz-627251247

1 years of experience in application development and deployment using java, spring web flux, React JS, etc. And experience in development of banking applications. Currently working on developing Agile backend, speaks both Thai and English. Interested in the end-to-end application development process

Education

May 2018 - Feb 2021

Bachelor of Science: Software Engineering
North Bangkok University, Bangkok

Feb 2013 - Jun 2018

High School Diploma

Sermpitayakhom, Nong Khai

Employment

Jul 2021 - Present

Application Development Associate

Accenture Thailand, Bangkok

I worked at Accenture for 1 year. I have been working on bank and loan projects. The tool I use is java (spring WebFlux). I take care of the development of EAPI with client's and common lib APIs so that my team can easily work with it.

Nov 2020 - Apr 2021

Freelance Programmer

SOLUTION POTENTIAL COMPANY LIMITED, Bangkok

I work for clients since the analysis of needs Up to the development and delivery process, it's 6 months. I use JavaScript for my project because it's a small project with not a lot of detail. So choose NodeJS and React tools for web app development.

Jul 2020 - Oct 2020

Java Developer

English

Motif Technology Public Company Limited, Bangkok

I working at the Thailand in Java Backend position at 4 mounts about design APIs with Client's EAPI and so on.

Skills

Java Spring boot reactive

Spring Security React

Kafka Kubernetes

Jenkin Git

MongoDb RESTful API

Languages

Thai

